

https://github.com/DHIRAJ540

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/dhiraj-subudhi-850365194/

About Me

Hey I am dhiraj currently pursuing b.tech in computer science. I am a web developer and ui/ux designer having experience of 6 months working in a realtime company environment. Frontend is my forte but I can handle simple backend programming.

Education

Khallikote University

2017 - 2019

Other Qualification-Science

National Institute of Science and Technology (NIST) Berhampur

2019 - Present

B.Tech-Computer science

Skills

Html

CSS

Javascript

Bootstrap

Reactis

React Native

Firebase

Node.js

Express js

MongoDB

Figma

Experience

Nimtler-Web developer

2021 - 2021

Worked here as a web developer and ui/ux designer. I redesigned and rebuild their websites and worked on some projects on ui designing.

Sarvvid-ai-Software developer

2021 - Present

I am working here as a software developer. I have built this companys mobile app (only frontend) and currently working on their websites.

Projects

My portfolio

It is my portfolio listing all my skills good projects and contact information about me.

Netflix clone

It is a clone of Netflix. It has almost all the features (only Frontend) that Netflix. I also implemented firebase authentication in It.

React games app

This is a games project where you can see and get information about any game. In this project I am getting data from an api and Integrating that with my Frontend.

Achievements

As achievements I dont have any certificates or course degrees. But I have experience. I have built some amazing websites and designs. I have worked in some big projects. If am working with someone and he is happy to work with me that is my real achievement.